Uh, I'm not sure. Stephanie, I don't
know if you know my partner. Great. Hi,
St. Nice to meet you. Nice to see you
guys. How's it going? Milling around.
Uh, well, have a seat.
What this is is
a I didn't want to bring this up in your
squadron.
Oh, no. It's fine. I think we're good to
We're bring You're going to bring
somebody in, right? Yeah. Well, explain
the whole thing, too.
I don't want to talk about this in the
squadron because I don't know who people
are listening. And if we go to my side,
everybody's always wondering what
everybody else is doing. Okay. But uh
like we're talking about being busy and
stuff, we've been assigned a case that
we've been looking at. Okay. It's a new
case and reviewing the case. There's
some notes to see as far as your name
being mentioned. Okay. Do you know John
Ruten?
John. John Rutton. Rutton. Rutton. Oh
yeah, I went to school with him. You
did? Yeah. How long did you know him?
Gosh, I went to school in um let's see,
went to UCLA in
1978. They started and um you know met
him at school at the dorms. Mhm. Um were
you guys friends? Close friends? Yeah,
we're very close friends. I mean, what's
this all about? Well, it's regarding
it's a case we're working on. It
involves John and in there some of the
statements we we reviewed uh you know,
there's notes and stuff that that he
knew you and stuff. Oh, yeah. I mean, we
good friends. Um lived in the dorms for
I lived in the dorms for 2 years. Um,
you guys lived in the same dorm? Yeah.
Oh, okay. Yeah, Dyra. Okay. Were you
guys just friends or anything else or?
Yeah, we were we were good friends.
Yeah. Was there any relationship or
anything that developed between you
guys? Yeah, I mean, we dated. Uh Uh-huh.
you know. Um I mean, is what's this all
about? Well, it's relating to uh his
wife.
Okay. Okay. Did you know her? Not
really. I mean, I knew that he got
married years ago. Uh-huh. Did you ever
meet her? God, I don't know. Um, do you
know who she was or anything? Well, I
Let me think. God, it's been a long time
ago.
Um Um, you know, I may have met her. Um,
jeez. You know. Yeah. Uh, well, let me
see. Let me ask you. You said you you
dated John. How long did you guys date?
I mean, well, are you guys is this
something I mean, you said I was going
to interview somebody about art and how
you guys are Here's I mean, Stephanie,
here's the situation is basically we,
you know, we knew that this when we saw
this in the in in this chrono that
maybe, you know, there was some
relationship there. That's what the
chrono seemed to indicate. And we didn't
want to come up to you at your desk and
ask those kinds of questions or do
anything. you know how up there people
can see what's going on if you go into
an interview room or people are in there
getting supplies. So we we wanted to
afford you some privacy, some
confidentiality to talk about this
because we thought it might be you know
something you know you're married to
someone else obviously and so forth and
that you may not want to you know talk
about these things in that setting where
someone you know we don't want the rumor
mill or gossip or any of that kind of
stuff. That's fine. I mean, so we we did
this just as as a means to try and speak
to you in just a confidential place
where you you know where where your
business isn't out there for other
people in you know your division. I
mean, you know, God, that's been a
million years ago. I mean, you know,
um what year is it now? 2009. I mean, I
graduated in ' 82. 82. Yeah.
Um you know, we dated um I dated other
guys. I'm sure he dated other girls. Um
Well, let me ask you roughly how long
would you would you say you guys dated?
Oh jeez.
Um, I couldn't even say. I mean, I
started school there in 78. I started
UCLA 1978. I graduated in ' 82. Um, I
don't even remember what year he
graduated, if it was a year or two
before me. Okay. Um, I think he was a
little bit older than I was. I mean, you
know, I can't remember if he was born,
let's say, I was born in 60, 1960. I
don't know if he was born in 58 or 59. I
mean, I, you know, um I mean, I knew his
parents. I knew his sister. His brother
went to Northridge.
Um um you know, his sister spent the
night at my house before. Obviously, I
spent the night at his house before. He
probably spent the night at my house
before. Um, you know, I I you know, I
don't Well, correct me if I'm wrong, cuz
from what you're telling me is you guys
dated while you were in college
together, right? Yeah. And probably
after college.
Um, I can't jeez. Um, trying to think
when I met my husband. I met my husband
in when did I meet Scott?
Um, let's see. I was teaching DARE
because I met Scott when I was teaching
DARE up in Oregon. But we had long
stopped, you know, dating before that.
So, you haven't talked to him for a long
time? Oh, I I think I haven't talked to
him in a long time. Um, I couldn't even
tell you when the last time I talked to
him. Um, I met Scott, I'm thinking in
'92, maybe. Um, April of '92. It was
Scott being your husband. Yeah. I'm
trying to think. I was teaching DARE.
Let's see. What year is this? This is
We'll be married. I got married in 1996.
I think I met Scott in '92. Prior to
that, I couldn't tell you how long I had
talked, you know, talked to John prior
to that. But since you since you met
your husband, Scott, you haven't talked
to him. I mean, he may have called me uh
once or twice before we got married,
right? Um, you know, gez, I I lived I
moved to see me in 1994 because I lost
my house in the earthquake. Oh. Um, uh,
quite honestly, I probably keep in
contact with a few people from the
dorms. We, we all, we all lived on the
10th floor. Um, and,
um,
there's about three or four people I
keep in contact with. There's probably
like six or eight of us that were all
really close. And who are those people?
Oh, jeez. Um, Diana Basta.
um the people I still keep I I haven't
been in contact with her in a long time.
Um I mean what you know what's what's I
mean what's this all about? I mean well
let me ask you what ended the
relationship between you and John you
know I don't it was kind of a weird
relationship. I mean we we we dated. Um
I can't say that he was my boyfriend. I
don't know that he would consider me his
girlfriend. Um we just we dated. We did
things. cuz I played sports in college.
He played basketball. His brother played
basketball.
Um, we just, you know, it
just didn't work out. I mean, I don't
know what to tell you. It was like I
went out with other guys. Um, saw other
guys. I went on lots of vacations. Um,
you know, and and once you guys split,
were you guys still friends or kind of,
you know, problems? Is it friendly? Not
friendly? No, I don't think it was not
friendly. I mean, we were friendly. Um,
uh, I know that we went to Hawaii
um, at one point. Um, another friend of
mine who's actually dying right now, uh,
was went to Hawaii with us, um, at some
point. Um, remember roughly when that
was? Oh jeez.
Um, let me
think. I'd have to check my pictures. Um
or I'd say I'd ask Greg, but my friend
Greg is like dying of liver cancer right
now. Um
yeah, I mean I you know and you were
saying that um it's 2009 now. Had you
ever met his wife?
I may have. Do you know do you remember
her name or anything or
um
or what she did for a living or where
she worked or anything about her? Well,
I think she I I'm going to say I think
she was a nurse.
Um, man, I can't even remember how he he
said he met her. Uh, yeah. I mean, I I
Yeah, I mean, it's been so long ago.
Well, let me ask you, did you go to
their wedding? You know, no, I didn't go
to their wedding. Um, no, I don't did
not go to their wedding. Um, couldn't
even tell you what year we got married.
I mean, you know, it's it's been a
million years ago. Do you ever remember
if you ever talked to her? cuz it seems
like a lot of you who were at at the
school at UCLA, you guys kind of were
friends during and after school. So, I
don't know if you guys still associated
afterwards when once he was married or
anything with him. Yeah. No, I don't
think so. I
mean, I would say, you know, the the
people that were on the dorm floor, we'd
have we'd have
gettogethers. Um there's probably like
four or five. I don't think he ever
came. Um, yeah. I don't think No, there
was there was like it was mostly girls,
you know. Um, girl named Smeita Diane.
Um, there's there's two Dian's, but the
one Diane, I don't think she ever came.
I kind of lost contact with her. We were
good friends on the floor. Um, yeah. I
mean, I don't you know, again, I I mean,
what you know, I don't understand why
you're talking about some guy I dated a
million years ago. Well, do you know
what happened to his wife? Yeah, I know.
She got killed. What did you What did
you hear about that? I I saw a poster at
work. Um I'm sure I spoke to him about
it.
Um I think I spoke to another friend of
his about it. Um and how did how did you
first learn about that?
Jeez. Someone could have called me. I
could heard it at work.
Um I think at one point there may have
been a flyer or something. I know a good
friend of his. is um Were you on the job
back then when that happened? Yeah, I
think so. Yeah, I'm sure I was on the
job. That's who I would have heard about
it with the flyer. Um he had a good
friend,
Mike Buldrick. Mike
um anyways, a he may have lived in the
dorms. I don't remember if that's how I
met him. Um I I may have talked to him.
I mean, you know, I don't remember how I
heard. I mean, I don't even remember
what year it was. And you think you you
thought you said you thought his wife
was a nurse. Do you have any idea where
she was working at the time or did he
ever mention that to you? Was it a
hospital or a doctor's office? I'm sure
he must have mentioned it now. Now that
you're bringing that up, I think she
worked at a hospital somewhere. And
yeah, I may have met her at a hospital.
Um I may have talked to her once or
twice. um at a at a hospital or more um
you know but being that you were kind of
you used to see uh John you know was it
everything okay between you guys? I mean
there wasn't every anything
uncomfortable or anything between you
and her?
Um you know I don't know. I mean it's
God it's been so many years. I
mean, uncomfortable. I
mean, I can't even I can't even remember
if we had a conversation. I mean, we may
have I may have I may have seen her at
his apartment, you know. Jeez, how many
years ago was that? I don't even know
what year she, you know, got killed.
Where was his apartment? On Rosco. Okay.
Yeah. Rosco in um
um east or west of do uh either east or
west of Dodto. Do you know where he
moved after did he move after he got
married or do you know or
I'm sure he did. Did you know where he
was living or
somewhere in the valley? Did you ever
visit him and his wife? No. No. never
went out, you know, get together,
dinners,
anything of that nature. Oh, no. Like I
said, his sister used to come over. His
sister had had come to my place. I knew
his I knew his brother cuz his brother
played basketball at Northridge. Um, in
fact, I was just coming across some
pictures that I just scan
uh scanned from
um I take a lot of photos. Um like
10,000. And I just did a service where I
scanned everything. Um, and I'd seen
some pictures of his brother playing
basketball. You just put them all on
your computer so you could have them
accessible and do things with them.
Well, my partner is a big photo thing
and he had a deal to scan. So, I spent a
ton of time just scanning photos. I
mean, I paid a company to do it. Mhm.
Um, so I've got photos of I mean his
brother, his sister, you know, 10,000
pictures. Oh, yeah. How long did that
take them? Months.
Now, what what do they do they put that
on a I'm just curious myself. And they
put it on they get get all on one DVD.
They don't need like a hard drive or
anything. No, no, there's like I think
11 DVDs. Yeah. I haven't even I don't
even have time. Oh, they It's a series
of DVDs that they put them on. Oh, yeah.
Okay. Yeah. I mean, I got I'm not that
familiar with computer stuff, so that's
why I was asking. It's like 11 DVDs. Oh,
okay. So, you know, um I haven't had a
chance to go through them. I I You could
go through and pick which ones you don't
want. I don't have time to do that.
Right. you know, so so like you said,
did I, you know, I I don't think we ever
socialized. Um, you know, he'd still
call me. Um, I can't say that I would I
mean, if he's married, I don't know that
I would have called him. I mean, maybe.
Who knows? I you know, I I don't know.
It's been a million years ago. How long
was John married before his wife died? I
couldn't I have no idea. I have no idea.
And uh after his wife died, did did you
talk to him again or or anything? Yeah.
I mean, I did talk to him. I talked to
him. Probably his parents. Um, probably
some other friends. Um, you
know, I'm sure I talked to him. Yeah.
Um, but you you don't you're not sure
where he moved to after he got married?
No idea. I mean, never went over to to
visit him or I don't think I mean, I
don't think so. I mean,
um I don't know. I don't I mean, I don't
think I did. Um, I mean I know he lived
on Rosco for a long long time.
Um, I mean he I may know I mean he may
have told me where they lived somewhere
in the valley. I mean he may have said I
lived over such and such but I I
couldn't tell you specifically where.
But you don't remember specifically ever
going over to visit him or visit them at
where wherever he moved when he left
Rosco? I I I honestly I don't know. I
don't think so. But okay, you know, I
don't want to say no, I don't think so.
And then he says, "Oh, yeah, she came
over for something. Drop something off."
You know, I'm I don't know. So, if you
did go over there, it just be like a a
quick thing like like you're saying,
"Drop something off or maybe?" Um, but
you don't remember as far as like going
there to have dinner or like a social
anything at the house, party? Well, if
you guys know something, I I just I
can't I don't know. I don't think so. I
mean, but after uh John's wife died and
you said you may have been talking to
him. Did uh your relationship start up
again? I would say no.
Um again, can you give me a year? I
mean, this is like 2009. She died in
1986. Yeah, I think it was 86. 1986.
Okay.
Um, like I said, I'm I'm faintly
remembering that
um I went to
Hawaii with my friend Greg. Greg and I
got certified for scuba
diving. Um, and I'm thinking that John
met us there, meaning Greg and I.
Um, that could have been I got
certified toward the end of 88 or I mean
20 yeah 88 89
um cuz I got reertified again and it had
been like
over 10 10 years. So I got reertified my
husband and I got reertified.
Um, and I'm pretty sure that John met us
there. Um, again, I'd have to tell you
what year it was. I'd have to look at my
pictures. Um, you know, um, and other
than that, I can't even say he may have
called me, you know, at my home. Um, I
may have called him. Um, I don't think
he got together with our group. Um, I
don't think Pat's his wife's desk. Uh
even before I don't you know we went to
weddings together. I you know did you
I've got pictures I like I said I
couldn't tell you years. It's been a
million years ago after he after he got
uh married or whatever. Were you were
you dating anybody
in particular let what year? 1986 you
said I think he got married in around
8586 something like that. Were you
seeing anyone seriously or?
God, I couldn't say.
Um, geez, I'm trying to think. I mean,
um, you know, I dated a fireman. Um,
what was his name? Mike Art. Um, and I'm
trying to think. Was he LFD or He was
LFD. Um, I'm trying to think when I went
I probably met Mike. I went to
Devincshire.
Let's see. I left Hollywood in 80. I I
worked Hollywood
84 to 85 I think and then I went to
Devonshire and that's when I met Mike
um and some other
firemen and what the station next door?
No actually cuz I used to work Hollywood
so I just wonder if it was the station.
No no it was in when I worked Devincure
I met Mike. Oh okay. All right. And I'm
trying to think. I went to Devonshire in
' 85 and I'm thinking
that I would have met him probably
sometime shortly after I went to
Devincure cuz I met him and his I
actually met his buddies at a fire.
Um and then Mike and I
dated, you know, just really kind of
casually. Um
and we remain very I mean we remain good
friends. Um you still in touch with him
or Unfortunately, he passed away. Oh,
really? He died in a um he had a car
crash. Um he did race cars and um he
went heading into a wall.
I couldn't tell you what year that was.
Um but he passed away. He was in a coma
and they pulled the uh the plug, right?
Seems like uh anyway. Um so, you know, I
couldn't even tell you what what year.
I'm thinking I went to Devon in 85 and I
know I met the guys because I it was
kind of a funny incident of how I met
them and that's how I remember it was
sometime probably 85 right um you know
specifically I don't even know if they
remember the other two are now married
to somebody else cuz I kind
of all three I mean did you kind of
socialize like when you were out with
Mike did those guys come out with you
too was it kind of like did you do stuff
with his friends or Well um there were
three there was two firemen Eric and
Gary um I met them first, then they
introduced me to Mike. So, that's how I
met Mike and Mike dated. Mike Mike and I
dated. Mhm. So, um and and not I
wouldn't even say I couldn't even tell
you for how long because then it would
say we decided you know it wasn't
working out and we'd be better friends
and you know he introduced me I think to
some other guy on that who now is on
LAPD. Um
uh Randy
Cordobus. Um, I don't think I know. He's
a detective. He's got a twin brother
who's on the fire department. That's how
I met Randy. Um, because he had a twin
brother, identical twin on the fire
department. Okay. Um, and you and I
dated him. When? I couldn't tell you. It
was before he came on the job. Oh,
before Randy came on the job. Yeah. Oh,
okay. And that was um I I'm God, I'm
trying to remember if Mike may
have I'm trying to remember. Mike may
have dated
um a girl that he
dated. Oh God, it sounds too weird.
Um, Randy may have dated a gal that Mike
was dating and that and then Mike Randy
broke up with that gal. I couldn't even
tell you the gal's name if I'm even
thinking of the story right. And then I
started dating Randy. Yeah.
I you know so again I mean not like I
was a huge floozy or anything but no but
you know I mean a lot of times right at
least from my female partners that I've
had you know it's hard dating guys that
aren't involved in kind of our circle
right because some a lot some guys are
intimidated by you know women police
officers yeah Randy was like an engineer
at the time uh he was like a some kind
of an engineer on a truck on a rig on a
fire truck No um an engineer um oh
professional engineer I think He lost a
job and then came on on the department.
I see. So, um, getting back to some
stuff, as far as you recall, after
John's wife died,
I did you start a relationship again
with with John or dating casually or
anything like that? Like I
said, he met Greg and I in Hawaii. Okay.
Um,
that was something you guys kind of
planned together like go as a group or
you ran into him or No, I I think that
obviously I must have talked to him and
I said, "Hey, I'm going to Hawaii with
my buddy Greg. We're we're sc we're
scuba we just got certified scuba
diving. Um, uh, we're going to be in
Hawaii. Hey, if you want to come and
join us, come join us." Right. And I I
think that's what it was. Um, I I may
have asked some other people to as well.
Um, you know, uh, what island did we go
to? I think the Big Island and Kauaii.
He either met us on the Big Island or
Kauaii. I'm thinking of SC Greg and I
might have scuba dived a lot in on the
Big Island as well as Kauaii. I'm I I
don't remember which island. Again, I'd
have to look at my pictures. Um, I
traveled a lot um, on my vacations. I
mean, I was always gone for at least a
month. Um, and I would go places and I
would either run into people or, you
know, you know, meet people. Um, and
Greg, this Greg we're talking about, he
was like someone you were dating or just
a buddy or No, you know what? I would I
would say we started out um probably
just buddies. Um, and either I was with
somebody or he was with somebody, but it
was all we it was kind of like we ended
up just kind of being like brother and
sister.
Um, and maybe he wanted something more,
but um, you know, it just it never, you
know, worked out, but we we we did
things together. Um, you know, I
consider them I've probably known
him, let's see, I've been on the job
almost 26 years. I've probably known
Greg 23, 24 years. Um, does he still
talk to him? Oh, yeah. He's dying of
liver cancer right now. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
sorry. Yeah. So, um, so, you know, I I
consider him a good friend. Um, you
know,
um, you know, I don't know what to tell
you on that. Um, I mean, when when you
heard about uh John's wife being killed,
I mean, what was your what was your
reaction? I mean, did you thought you
heard about it what through a friend or
in a bulletin or something? you're a
friend or a bulletin. Um I obviously I
mean I called I called the family. Um I
I called maybe some of his friends that
that that I knew and I mean obviously it
shocked you if you're if I heard it at
work, you know. Um which I may have I I
faintly remember a bulletin going
around. Um either that or somebody
called me. I I also don't remember.
Right. Um uh and then I called probably
called his family. um called uh I don't
initially I can't say if I initially
spoke to him or not. I honestly don't
remember. I may have said to somebody,
"Hey, have him call me if he wants to
talk." And then he may have done that.
Uhhuh. Um you know, um
do you know what the circumstances
regarding her death?
Jeez, let me think back.
Um, jeez. I don't know if it was, you
know, if it was a burglary or something.
Uh, yeah, it's I mean, it's been so many
years. I I mean, I can faintly think
that I may have saw a flyer. Yeah. May
have had her picture on it, you know.
Um, I may That's why I say if somebody
had called me, I may not have known what
her last name was. I may have I mean,
maybe if you told me, I would remember
it. Um, do you remember her first name?
Shelly um
Sherry I don't know something maybe you
know um like I said it's been so many
years and um from all the years as far
as you can remember you don't do you
remember ever talking to her just well I
said earlier you know I I mean I may
have you know I may have talked to her
um I it sound I you know you mentioned a
hospital maybe you may have talked to
her at a hospital.
Yeah. Um, yeah, I may have, you know,
I'm I'm thinking back now you guys are
bringing up all these old memories. No,
I kind of dust off the conversation, you
know. I mean, jeez.
Um, I'm thinking
that because I mean, we would date, he
would date other people, I would date
other people. Mh. And I think, you
know, at one point, I mean, he may have
been dating her or I don't know, maybe
he was married. I don't even remember.
And I'm like, you know what? Why are you
calling me if you're either dating her
or living with her or married to her? I
I cuz I honestly don't remember the time
frame. Um, and I'm like, come on, knock
it off. And I'm And now I'm thinking I
may I may have gone to her and say,
"Hey, you know what? You know what? Is
he dating you? He's he's bothering me."
Um, and so I'm thinking that we had a
conversation about that.
Um, one or two maybe. I, you know, it
could have been three. I don't want to
say I had three conversations with her
like at her work or at their at their
house or No, I'm thinking that I, you
know, he obviously must have told me
where she worked. I'm thinking it was a
hospital somewhere in LA. And I just I
mean, I could have been again, what year
was that? Where was I working?
Um, you know, I don't I don't I'm trying
to think of where I when did you say
they got married?
I don't know. I think it was like in '
85 or '86 or something like that. Yeah,
we we we just kind of picked this up.
We, you know, we don't know a lot about
it.
1945. I mean, I could have been working
in Hollywood, it sounds like, if if
that's where I was working. Um, so I
could have said, "Okay, well, you know,"
and I went talked to her. Um, and just
said, "Hey, you know what? You know, if
he's dating you, he's he's keeps calling
me. Why don't you tell him to knock it
off or whatever?" And you know, because
I probably would have told him to knock
it off. Who would have told John? Oh,
yeah. I mean, I would have said, "Hey,
you know," and again, but you wanted to
tell her, too. You wanted them both to
know. Yeah. I mean, you know, if you get
you're getting her called and I'm trying
I'm faintly remembering uh when Scott
moved in with me in
1993, sometime in '93, cuz I met Scott
in in
in April of '92. I was teaching Dare Up
in Oregon. Mhm. Um and
um he moved down. In fact, he may have
moved down in '92. 92 or 93. There was a
big earthquake. No. When was the big
earthquake? No. 94. 94. Yeah.
I think Scott might have moved into 93.
Sometime in
93. Excuse me. Um I haven't had my
breakfast yet. Um, and so,
um, excuse me. Um, and so I faintly
recall that John may have called a few
times and I'm like, hey, you know, I've
got, he goes, can you I like you, can
you talk or something? I'm like, you
know, no, I can't talk. I've got, you
know, I'm living with somebody, right?
You know, and and that could have been a
few times. It could have been once,
could have been twice, could have been
three times. I don't know, you know. Um,
that's during the period of time of the
earthquake that you're Well, no,
probably probably after Scott moved in.
I think I met Scott in April of '92. Oh,
okay. Right before April of '92 cuz I
was I I stopped teaching DARE
think I stopped teaching Dare sometime
in '92. Mhm. Um,
and when you and when you say that you
may have um, you know, that you talked
to his wife, said, "Hey," or, you know,
I don't know if it was I guess it wasn't
his wife at that time, girlfriend or
whatever. And yeah, I don't know if it
was his wife or I I I mean, quite
honestly, I don't even remember when you
said like, "Hey, you know, he's calling
me. He needs to knock it off or what
have you." I mean, was that was that
civil? Was there I mean, oh, yeah. No,
there was not. I don't think there was
anything. It was the conversation
lasted a few minutes. I can't even
remember. And what is it like, you know,
we went out to lunch or anything, right?
But there was no like arguments or
fights or it didn't get heated or
anything like that. Not that I recall.
No. I mean, I would think that would
stand out. I would think. Now, again,
that's not standing out in my mind.
Um, you know,
so you didn't have any problems with her
then? You didn't have any issues with
her? No. I mean, but let me let me ask
you, seems like you didn't have any
issue. Now, did she have an issue with
you as far as because now you're telling
her, "Hey, you know, tell him to stop
calling now." You know, she's like,
"Hey, you know, you figure she'd be
threatened by you?" You know, I've I
don't know. I mean, from what you
remember as far as when you talked to
her, maybe you didn't take it as
serious, but maybe, you know, did she
was bugging? You mean like was she
throwing things at me or something? Or
Well, no. Just, you know, as far as
you're trying to explain like, "Hey,
stop calling me, you know, stop playing
games." You know, I I tell you I if the
conversation I couldn't even tell you
how long the conversation if you said
did it last a half an hour, did it last
3 minutes? Did it last 20 minutes? I
can't even remember. It's been so long
ago, you know. Um you just remember
talking to her, telling her. Yeah. And
that's why you said how many times you
talked to her. I don't know how many
times I talked to her. Maybe it was
once, maybe it was twice, maybe it was
three times, you know. I I honestly
don't know. Um I I don't know what year
it was. Um, if you if he said, "I met
her in such and such year," I'd go,
"Okay." Well, I don't even know what
year he met her. Um, I graduated from,
you see, in 1982. Okay. I graduated in '
82. Like I said, I don't know if he
graduated. I know he was a little older
than I was. So, I don't know if he
graduated a year before or two years
before because people are on different
um either on the four-year program or
the 5-year program. Um, what year did
you come on the job? 83. Oh, so almost
pretty much immediately after you got
out of school. Yeah, I worked at a law
firm for a year. Um, and then came on
the job. But anyway, in regards to
seeing him, not seeing him, we went to
friends weddings that were, you know,
from UCLA. Um, I may have gone to some
of his friends weddings from where he
worked. Um, he may have gone to things
with me, you know.
Um, you know, I mean, I I don't know how
many times we went to do things, you
know, or didn't do things, right? Like I
said, his sister, um, um, I know his
sister, uh, his brother, his sister, I
know, stayed at my
townhouse a number of times. I couldn't
tell you how many times, right? Um, I
would watch his brother, you know,
shoot, uh, take pictures at a basketball
game or or two. Where was your townhouse
at? In Granada Hills. Um, below the
Odyssey. I don't know. Oh, I'm sorry.
The 405 and the five. Um, the 405 the
the 405 turns into the five, the 118.
Um, they they came down in the
earthquake. Okay. So, Okay. And you're
saying when you went to see her, do you
would you remember if it was at her
house or at the place she worked at?
No, I'm thinking that I'm thinking that
it was
probably for some reason I want to say
that the hospital seemed that, you know,
if you say he got married in 85 or
something, I'm thinking that, you know,
maybe the hospital was on my way to work
in Hollywood. I mean, that's kind of
sounding familiar. Um, would you have
gone on duty? Oh, no. I'm I'm sure I
wouldn't have. I No, I'm I'm pretty good
about not doing stuff, you know. I mean,
now I'm not saying that, you know, you
haven't done stuff on duty, but I I I
would have I mean, I would have been
working with somebody. Oh, yeah. You
know, so I wouldn't I wouldn't think I
mean, I try to avoid doing stuff on
duty. So, so you would have gone if it
was in route to work, you more than
likely you would have gone to her work
and had this discussion with her. I
mean, that's sounding familiar. I mean,
that's now that you guys are bringing
this stuff up. Um, I mean, it sound that
sounds familiar. Um, but again, I mean,
you
know, what's I mean, what's this got to
do with me dating him and, you know, her
getting killed? I mean, I I don't, you
know, I don't have anything to do with
it. And you got something that's
somebody said, you know, whatever. I
mean, well, like we said, we we just
literally got this the other day and and
you're going through it. Yeah. And you
see, you saw me say, "Oh, it's Nick's
next door." Right. And and so, you know,
I mean, obviously, it's like we
recognize the name. We know, you know,
you work next door to us and so we're
trying to get some background. We're
trying to figure this out. I mean, this
is from a long time ago. Oh, I know. You
know, and and things have been kind of
slow for us and so, you know, Chief Beck
has said, "Hey, you know, I want you
guys working. I don't want you just
sitting around reading the paper." So,
he's kind of pushing some older cases
out even to the guys that work active
cases because, you know, and so we see
this and we're just like, "Oh, well, you
know, we want to talk to you about it."
But, of course, the only reason we did
it here is because we're getting into
some pretty personal stuff in your
relationship. You know, my my husband's
on the job and we've been married. You
know, we don't want to take the risk. We
don't want to take the risk. We're in
one of those interview rooms and even
when the door closed, someone's going to
get supplies and see us on a monitor
here or whatever. I appreciate it. I
mean, I appreciate, like I said, that's
where people go when there's orals, you
know, when they're doing orals, guys
will go in there and try and watch. What
are the answers to the questions, you
know? I didn't know that. Yeah. So, so
we just we just want to afford you the
most privacy and confidentiality we
could. No, I appreciate and like I said,
I mean this goes way back and I mean it
was very sad, you know, obviously
um I I haven't I you know I when we were
in college, some of us would go down to
his house in San Diego. I I went down to
his house with him, you know, um with
with him. And I know I I'm trying to
think of some other people that may have
gone down. Is that where he grew up? Is
down there? Yeah, down in San Diego.
Okay. Um I know his dad's was a
professor at San Diego State. I don't
know if he still is. Mhm. Um I don't
know what happened to his sister. Don't
know what happened to his brother.
Um you know, I'm sure his dad's probably
retired by now. He was I think older. Um
even back then, right? Um and I I can't
even tell you the last time I had any
contact with any of them. It's been so
long. Did he tell you what happened?
Like what he heard from the detectives
or the police or
You know what? He may have
um for some reason I'm thinking that I
mean again this is
like drugs or something. I mean I think
I faintly remember him mentioning
something maybe about cocaine
um that she was involved with that. You
know, I don't know that he said she was
involved or they thought she, you know,
again, it's been so long. I, you know,
he could have mentioned, he could have
told me the whole story of what
happened. And I mean, like I said, I'm
faintly remember either between him or
the flyer. Um, that there was some kind
of a burglary. Um,
you know, let me ask, did the detectives
ever reach out to you ever? No. No one's
ever talked to me. I don't think anybody
ever talked to me about about him. Um,
it seems like back. Well, I I
take I'm thinking that I did talk to a
detective. Um,
God Well, what division was it in Van
Ice?
And where was I working?
Um, 1986.
I would have been working Devonshire.
You know, I'm thinking that I did speak
to somebody. Oh, really? I couldn't tell
you who it was because it doesn't it
doesn't say anything. Probably on the
phone. Okay. Um would it have been
somebody in regards to this or just
Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah. Um
I don't even know if you said a name if
I would remember it because I worked Van
Ice for a while. Oh, you did? Yeah, I
worked um detectives patrol. No, worked
detectives. Uhhuh.
Um when did I go to Van
Ice? I worked Devonshire till 88. Then I
went to DAR till
92. I worked twice at Van Ice. Um both
as a detective.
Yeah. Sometime in the '9s.
Um, yeah. I I know before I busted my
leg up, I was there in '98 cuz that year
sticks out because I had a really bad
leg injury.
Um, and I was there prior to that, but I
couldn't tell you what year. It was just
a few years. I made detective I think in
93 93. So,
um, I was at Van Eis and then I went
back and then I had a leg injury and
then they transferred me to Devonshire
cuz I couldn't drive. Mhm. I couldn't
drive very far with the my bad leg
injury. So,
um, but yeah, I I I think I talked to
somebody. Um, remember would you
remember any of the conversation as far
as what they were looking for?
Couldn't say. I mean, they may have told
me. I said, "Hey, you know, I went to
school with him. Um, I either they
either somebody called me or I saw the
fly. I may have seen the flyer at that
point and I called up. If if someone's
name was on the flyer, I may have called
to speak to them." I said, "Hey, if
there's anything I can do, you know, um,
call me. This is where I work. You know,
I went to uh, you know, uh, school with
them."
Um, couldn't say I couldn't tell you who
it was.
But you do remember that that someone
you think reached out to you.
You mean a detective? Yeah. Called you
up and talked to you or I called them.
One of the two. But yeah, I you know I I
remember talking to somebody
but I'm thinking it was a man. I'm sure
there's probably more men back then.
Um
so again that's I mean that's really all
I can remember about that.
Yeah. Let me get back uh to as far as
when you said that uh John was calling
you to to see you and during that time
you felt that he was was felt he was
either seeing her was he engaged or
married. Did did you know? Could say you
remember you know I don't know. Uhhuh.
Um would he ever Well, let's see. My
husband did it ever appear? Well, no.
No, that would have been Scott moved in
93. So that would have been you said '
86 or ' 85 or something. Scott, your
only husband. You've never been married?
No, never been. I got married in I think
96. Oh, no. I No, I got married in 96,
but he moved in in 93. Mhm. But, uh,
during that time that you were seeing
John, uh, you know, was he acting kind
of, you know, kind of squirrely or kind
of sneaking around when he'd hook up
with you or anything like that? Does it
make you think, hey, yeah, he probably
was. I mean I mean cuz from the
impression I get you've known him a long
time. Well, let's see from what early I
met him in 78. No, I I met him in
school. I started UCLA in 78. Um so you
know him
well during that period of time. Yeah. I
mean was he acting
squirrely? You know I don't even
remember where he was living then. You
know I Well, after I don't Well, let me
ask you after he hooked up with uh if he
was living on Rosco or wherever else he
was living, right? Well, after he hooked
up with uh with Sherry, do you know uh
where they were living? No, you asked me
that already. Uhhuh. And I said, well,
obviously they were living in Van I
division. Yeah.
Um I may have known. I mean I you know
again I you know did he ever give me the
address? Maybe you know I don't
remember. I mean, I don't know
cuz the only reason I'm asking you again
is because as we've been talking, I know
some stuff has come to you cuz you're
like, "Oh, see, you know, so that's why
I'm asking if you ever been to the
house." And when you said Van Eyes
vision, you know, I'm
just I'm sure he could have told me. I
mean, he could have told me. He could
have told me where he lived. Um,
do you ever have gone there? I don't
think I've ever gone there. That's what
I'm saying. I don't I don't want to say
no, I've never gone there and then you
say, "Oh, I was at a party." I cuz I I I
don't, you know, I don't think so. Yeah.
Um, like I said, we've got these
friends. We have different We have
parties. Um, my house, their house. I I
just don't think John ever came to
again, you know, at one point because we
we knew people from school together. I
knew different people. He knew different
people. I knew people that he knew from
his work um you know that lived in the
valley.
Um you know,
so as far as for social events or
anything, I mean it's I mean you're not
sure if you ever been to the house cuz
But it's safe to say that would have
been the only time like for something
social.
Yeah. If I went there for something
social. Yeah. I mean, because I know you
you went to talk to her at at the
hospital uh regarding this issue with
John to, you know, kind of like, hey,
you know, what's going to happen here
with this thing? But would this ever
have followed up to her house when you
went to talk to her to say, hey, you
know what? I I don't even know that I
knew where they lived. I You know,
that's what I'm saying. I don't If I
knew where they lived and I'd been
there, if it was for something social,
I' I would I'm I'm And I can't see how
many times I I saw her face to face. You
know, he lived on Rosco. Did I ever see
her there? I don't know. I mean, I may
have seen her at his apartment on Rosco.
Mhm. I may have met her
there, you know. I I mean, but you
didn't have any issues with her, right?
No, I mean, you know, obviously if he
was dating me and dating her, I probably
said, "Hey, pick." Or something, you
know, you know, back then.
Um, I can't say that we ever screamed or
Yeah. You know, it's I mean, he was a
pretty mellow guy, you know. Um, I think
I was pretty mellow. I I don't I don't
think we had some big huge blow up to
say you know why we stopped dating or
you know and I even think that when I
was dating him I was probably like I
said I was probably going out with other
guys and he was probably going out with
other girls you know I don't know I mean
would you remember if she snapped on you
and just like hey man it's my man you
know you get leave him alone you know
blah blah blah that kind of stuff you
know
then would you remember an incident like
that I mean cuz that would be like what
Well, you know, and maybe that happened.
I
mean, gosh, I you know, it's been so
long ago. I, you know, I just I mean,
that's not ringing a bell. Mhm. Um I
mean, because the times I've seen you
around at our office, I'm crazy, you
know, but you're always kind of like
real I mean, you seem kind of bubbly.
Oh, I'm you people think I'm really
hyper. Um, but I can I mean I can get I
can get upset, you know, and and then I
forget 5 seconds later, you know, you
know how guys raz you and you go, "Ah,
you know, um I mean I've done that in
the office, you know, but it's like and
then I'm, you know, and then I'm, you
know, uh, you know, I mean, under the
bridge. Yeah. I mean, it's like people
think I'm crazy and then they think I'm
crazy at home and I'm, you know, more
I'm I'm a hyper person at work. I'm, you
know, I enjoy my job. I get excited. I,
you know, um I I enjoy the job. I've
always enjoyed the job. Um Well, you got
a good gig. So, you know, um so, you
know, I you know, I don't know. It's
like, like I said, this stuff's been so
long ago. Um you know, I'm sure as soon
as I walk out of here, I'll go, "Oh,
shoot. I 25 things I'll remember." Um
you know, but you'll call us or I mean,
you'll just come over to our desk and
tell us. I mean, I don't know what else
you need to know. Like I said, you know,
we we knew friends together. A lot of
the friends that, you know, that we
socialized in the dorms, I would say, I
mean, there was a group of us that
um we were all really close. I mean,
even this one guy, I was thinking of,
you know, um Diana Basta. We were all
really close. I haven't talked to her in
a million years. Um Diana Basta being a
friend of you and John's or Yeah, we all
lived on the dorms on the dorms
together. I don't know if she lived on
the same we I'm trying to think. I think
I know John lived on our floor because
his roommate was Dave Newman. Dave
Newman now is a big huge big shot
whatever movie producer director
something I don't know. Um and that was
John's roommate. Yeah. And then the guys
that lived across from me um Jim Jascal
and
Roy Sakaboo Sakaboo. Something like
that. Um they lived across from me. Um
Diana
Basta. I don't know if she lived on our
floor. Maybe she was the
RA. Um Diane Sherman. Um cuz I still
remain friends with Diane Sherman. Um
not that I'm not friends with the other
people. I just don't see them. Um a girl
named
Smeita. Um
Sally, Kathleen, you know. So we we were
all on the floor. I mean, some of them
were athletes, some of them weren't. You
know, I said John played basketball, his
brother played basketball, I played
basketball at UCLA for two years. Um,
one of the girls swam on the team, one
was on the crew team. So, we all did
stuff together. Um, and then I'd say
after we all graduated, um, we went to
weddings, you know, I went to weddings.
Um,
uh, but Sherry wasn't part of this
circle. No, I don't even know how he how
he met her. I don't even know where I
mean, I don't know where he met her
from. I don't even know. He told me
where he met her from. I mean, he may
have told me. I, you know, that's not
ringing a bell.
Um, and there was lots, I mean, you
know, there's just there was other
people that knew other people, um, you
know, that were friends of everybody's
um, you know,
um, I mean, I don't know what else to
tell you. Well, one of the concerns I
had is looking at some of the notes is
uh some of Sherry's friends said that
you and her were having a problem
because of the John situation.
Well, number one, I don't know who her
friends are. Um cuz again, I don't I
don't recall if he did tell me where he
met
her. I don't even know who these friends
are. a problem. Like I said, if I spoke
to her, I mean, I'll go on as far as a
limb and I don't even want to say I
spoke to her five times because that's
probably not even true. I I I can't even
remember.
Um, again, did I meet him at her plate
when he, you know, he lived on Rosco for
I think quite a while, but I couldn't
tell you how long he lived on Rosco. And
the only reason why I remember the place
now is because it's like a huge dope
dope place now where they, you know, it
may have been back then, but you know,
maybe we'd have known back then. Um, I
could have met her there. I could have,
you know,
you know, I don't even know that I met
any of their friends. I I don't I I I
can't say that. I don't know that that's
a true statement. Well, that's what I'm
reading is that you guys had problems
with each other and words are being
exchanged and it's all relating to John.
You know what? I I I I just I can't say.
You can't say? No. I That doesn't even
ring a bell. I mean I mean it seemed
like Yeah. You would recall something if
somebody's going off on you, right? I
would think. I mean I would think I
would think. Yeah. cuz it's But that's I
you know cuz it seems like your
relationship with John was kind of I
mean you've known each other for a lot
of years. Yeah. It was just kind of it
was like
but it doesn't seem to me from what you
tell me I mean we were never engaged. I
mean it wasn't like we were planning to
get married. Um you know it was like it
it
was I don't know how to describe it. I
mean, would you say there wasn't a lot
of drama in this relationship? Oh, no. I
don't think there was drama. Okay. Yeah.
I mean, that's why I'm asking as far as
what the friends are saying in regards
to this, you know, the problems that
they're saying you were having with with
Sherry.
I mean, it seems like the relationship
is just going on even plain. That just I
I that I don't have a recollection of
that at all. No. No. And cuz from what
you're telling me is when you guys met
at the hospital,
uh I mean you guys talked but it wasn't
from what you recall confrontational
think from either side. No, I I mean I'm
trying to you know turn my memory back,
you know, and I'm trying I can't even
can't even picture the you know picture
the the conversation. I mean I can't
even picture the conversation. Well, let
me ask you. I mean, at the hospital, it
never got to the point where people are
going, "Hey, hey, you know, go to
everybody go to your own culinary type
of thing." I don't think so. Nothing
like that. I don't think so. I mean, I
really don't. I mean, if you, you know,
if you say people said that, that's not
ringing a bell to me at all. I mean,
it's not I mean, that that's not ringing
a bell. Was there ever a time when you
and Sher were talking and John had to
maybe like get you guys relax, you know,
or anything like that? I think
so. about, you know, ever going to a
house and having a dispute like that.
You know, I'm
just if I met her ever at his apartment,
maybe I mean, we could have met I could
have met at her apartment. I'm thinking
that the hospital thing that sounds
familiar that I I met her
there. I just can't say that I've ever
again, was I there with other people? I
don't I I it I don't know. Um I don't
think I ever met her there or him there.
Um meaning one or the other. I don't
think so. I really I just I can't I
don't think so. Cuz I mean I know the
way my wife is at our house, she
wouldn't want my own girlfriends there,
you know. So, I don't know if maybe she
had the same mentality towards you. If
as far as you ever being there or being
welcome there, you know, because it's
you know what, if somebody said I was
there when they were there, then that's
possible, but I just I I don't recall. I
mean, I don't think so. I don't I It's
not sounding familiar. Yeah. Cuz I guess
basically what I'm asking is, you know,
were you ever welcomed to the house?
Like, you know, hey Oh, come over. Yeah,
come on over. We're having a barbecue,
you
know, a dinner party. Christmas party or
whatever. I don't know. I'm just trying
to
think, you know, like I said, because
there was so many of us that the two
Dian's U, Jim, Jascal, Roy, um, Smeita,
this gal, Smeita, another friend of
ours, Beth, I she pass, it seems like
everybody I know pass is passing away.
Um, she passed away. She was a child
diabetic and and got very ill. Um, we
would all socialize. Um, like I said, I
don't think John ever it's hard. I don't
want to say he never socialized with us.
Um, you know, it it's been I I'd have to
go almost go back and look at pictures
because I take pictures. I mean, I
usually when I have I go to functions, I
have 10,000 pictures. Okay. I'm a
picture nut.
Let me ask when you were seeing John,
would you I take it he would pick you up
in his car. you go in her, you know,
your car, things of that nature when you
guys would go out.
Well, yeah. I mean, do you remember what
he what he drove?
Well, I know at one time he drove either
a 240 or 260Z.
Any other cars that stand out in your
mind?
[Music]
I don't know how long he drove that 240
or 260Z for. Um, and the only reason I
say that is cuz I think I may have a
picture of it um with him in it. Um,
what kind of car did you have back then?
Let's see. What year? Or are you like
one of those young cops that like, "Oh,
I got a paycheck and bought a new car."
No, no, no. I've only had like a few
cars in my whole life. So, what'd you
have when you came on the job?
Okay. Well, my first car was a 68
Chevel. 68
Chevel. And then I
had a
Toyota some kind of a Toyota. Mhm.
Um hatchback, but I forget what the name
of it was. Um like a Corolla or Tursel
or Tursel. Something like that. Tel.
Yeah. And then I had my truck. Do you
ever have any problems with your cars?
Like what? Just anything in general. Car
wrecks. Anything stolen? Yeah. No, my
car has never been stolen. Oh, no.
Crashed, hit and run. Um
um hit I mean my tcel was hit and run.
Again, I got I got pictures of the hit
and runs. Um and I don't think any of my
cars had ever been stolen. No, my cars
haven't been
stolen, broken
into. Um, none of that, huh? Oh, yeah.
They My cars have been broken into.
Um, you know, but no cars have ever been
stolen.
Mhm. How long? Well, when Tell me about
this uh car getting broken into. Well,
my car has been broken into several
times. Oh,
really? Did you ever lose anything or?
Yeah, now that you mention it, let's
see. I had a gun that was stolen. Mhm.
Um, I had other stuff that was stolen.
Not a duty gun, was it? No. Oh, that's
good. Um, has it ever recovered? I don't
No, no, I don't think so. Not that I
know of. Never been notified. No. Car's
been broken
into Yeah. several times. Where did that
happen? when your gun was taken.
Trying to remember.
I'm sure you guys must know.
Um cuz my car was broken into in
Ventura. I think in Santa Monica. I have
relatives that live in Santa Monica and
Venice. Um who lives there? My uncle.
Well, I I had several uncles.
Um, yeah, could have been Santa Monica.
Um, Venice. My My car's been broken into
in Ventura before.
So, is your mom still around or Mhm.
Yeah. Your dad? Yeah. But I don't really
have much of a relationship with my dad.
So, I couldn't tell you where he lives
if you're if you want to know. Oh,
really?
No. Yeah, I couldn't tell you.
Well, like I said, as we were looking at
the case and you know, we had read the
notes as far as from uh Sherry's friend
saying you you guys had problems or
words, they got
heated. You know, the reason we're
asking you is they had mentioned that an
incident at her work had occurred and
they've also told us that an incident at
her house occurred.
You know what? And this is at her house
during the period of time that they're
married.
That's just not sounding familiar at
all. I mean, I you know what
I that's just not sound I again if
someone says that I was at her house and
I had an incident with
her, you know, I that just doesn't sound
I I you know, was John there? Did John
say this happened? Because And other
people were there. I I just I don't
recall. I mean, it just doesn't sound,
you know, familiar. And this is an
incident where you showed up. You
weren't supposed to show up and things
got heated at his house? Yeah.
That I you know I that just doesn't
sound familiar. I mean
I you know it's not sounding familiar.
So not at all. Now you're saying not
familiar because it's just don't you
remember or it's just you know what I
would have then I'd have to say I don't
remember because I don't remember I that
doesn't sound familiar. I I mean would
you remember something like that in your
life if Well I would think but some sort
of drama involving you know the other
woman type of thing. Did you ever fight
with her? You mean like we fought? Yeah.
Did you ever duke it out with her? No, I
don't think so. I mean you'd remember
that, right? That would be pretty Yeah,
I would think so. Oh, I mean pretty
specific. Yeah, like I said, I mean
obviously I you know I mean it just
doesn't sound familiar. I mean I mean
what are they saying? So I I I fought
with her so so now I mean I I get
getting the jump or the leap. Excuse me.
I haven't eaten. Um they're saying okay
I fought with her so I must have killed
her. I mean come on. I mean that's you
know I don't even know who these people
are. I I can't even say I met any of
these people. I mean, that's it's
insane. I I if it happened, I honestly
don't remember it. That's all I can tell
you. I mean I mean, but I don't know. I
mean, would it be something you would
remember? I mean, because it's I don't
know if any other intense incidents in
your life that have occurred, I mean,
you'd recall those, right? I mean, well,
like a use of force at work or car
crash, something you're involved in,
you'd be like, "Yeah, I remember." You
would think I would remember. I mean, I
would think if it was something that
crazy. I mean, I I can't say you say how
many fights have you gotten into, you
know, in your
life, you know? I mean, a few at work.
Well, fights at work are kind of
different cuz we've all had uses of
force or whatever, but I mean, I don't
even have even a lot of those. I mean,
but if you're if you're actually, you
know, I mean, I've played like if if Dan
and I got mad at each other and we threw
blows in the squad room, I mean, 20
years later, I would remember it. I
mean, I would think I would remember it,
but that's that's what I'm saying.
That's not sounding familiar to me at
all. I mean, I Let me ask you. I mean,
throughout your
life, you know, would you remember the
number of fights you've been involved
in? And I don't mean kind of like a bump
or something, just a a physical fight
where
you everybody's hitting each other,
scratching, pulling, you know, whatever.
Maybe. I mean, I can't say I've been in
a lot. You know, I played sports. Yeah.
you know, you get into scuffles there
and
um and you recall some of those, right?
I mean, just Yeah, I can recall some of
them. Yeah. Games get in tabs. But like
I said, this you saying this this is
just not ringing a bell. I mean, but you
know, I don't know what to tell you.
It's It's just That's just not ringing a
bell to me. It' be something I would
think I would remember. I mean, I'm If
you're in this, too. If you're in this
other girl's house and words are
exchanged, I mean, you figure you'd
recall. I would think, especially if it
got physical, right? Well, I would
think. And it's relating to, you know, a
guy that you were dating, but she's
dating now, you know, and it's just like
a whole love triangle type of thing. I
mean, you figure you'd remember that,
right? Well, I would think.
So,
I mean, what does she tell you? Yeah.
No, because I'm I mean I'm trying to I'm
looking at the notes and these people
are kind of I mean they're pointing the
finger at you. Well, and I mean that's
not ringing a bell to me. So, you know,
I don't know. You know,
it's I don't know what to tell you. I
mean, that just sounds crazy to me.
Yeah. So, you offh hand you don't recall
ever going into her house and having
words and
physically, you know? No. attacking her,
her attacking you. No, nothing like
that. No, I mean that's No, nothing. No,
no, not at all.
Okay. Well, on some of the uh on this
case, you know, this is it occurred in '
86, right? Uh detectives processed the
scene, things of that nature. Uh they
did fingerprints and all that stuff. You
know, well, you know, the standard
stuff. I mean, you been doing this
longer than I have. Uh well I don't know
about that. I got 26 years on going on
26 19. So
but you know as they processed
everything uh they did the best they
could at that time and they looked at a
lot of a lot of people and different
things in this case and you're right. I
mean if you guys are claiming that I'm a
suspect then you know I I got a problem
with you know with that. Okay. Okay. So
you know if you're if you're doing this
as an interrogation you're saying hey
I'm a suspect. Well, now I got a problem
with, you know, now you're accusing me
of this. Is that what you're Is that
what you're saying? We're trying to
figure out what happened, Stephanie.
Well, I'm I was, you know, I'm just
saying, you know, would I need to get a
lawyer if you're accusing me of, you
know, you don't have to I mean, you
know, you're here of your own free will.
I mean, well, I know, but you know,
you're not you're not under arrest. You
can walk out when you can leave whenever
you like. Well, you know, I I'm trying
to give you some background of, you
know, how I knew him and now you're
telling me that some somebody's saying
that we had this big old fight and I
don't even know what you're talking
about. Um, you know, and I don't want
to, you know, get in trouble for
something that I didn't even do or
you're saying I did something. Okay, we
understand. I mean, how would you guys
like it if the tables were turned on
you? I understand. No, that's why we're
telling you. I mean, you're free to go
whenever you want. If if this makes you
uncomfortable and you want to now you're
starting to make me uncomfortable. The
thing is I mean detectives did what they
could at that time on the crime scene.
Okay. And the burglary thing you're
talking about that is an angle that they
looked at. I go but now we're looking at
everything else on the case cuz nobody
was ever arrested on the case. I I don't
know that or not. Okay. Now what we'd
like to do is obviously you know about
all the DNA stuff and things of the
nature that you know gets done on cases
nowadays. You know, if we asked you for
a DNA swab, would you be willing to give
us one?
Maybe because now now
now I'm thinking I probably need to talk
to a lawyer. Okay. I mean, well, I cuz I
know how this stuff works. Okay, don't
get me wrong. You're right. have been
doing this a long time and and I wish I
had been recording this because because
now it sounds like, you know, there's,
you know, you're selling these people
saying I'm a fighting with her and now
it sounds like you're trying to, you
know, I've been doing this a long time.
Yeah, we know. Okay. And and now it
almost sounds like you're trying to pin
something on me now. I I got that sense.
Well, what it gets to on these on these
cases, and you know it as well as I do,
our job is to identify and eliminate
substance. I can't believe this. So, if
we ask you to the point to give us a DNA
sample, a bugal swab, so we can identify
or eliminate you, would you be willing
to do that? Maybe.
Cuz I know this. I I I I That's where
we're at, too. I mean, because right now
from looking at the evidence, it's, you
know, it's possible we may have some DNA
at the location. That's great.
And we're going to do what we can to try
to put this thing together. and your
name's in the book. These people are
pointing at you for whatever reason. I
don't know why. That's just crazy. I
mean, that's just that's absolutely
crazy. And it would be irresponsible on
our part not to look at it. I know. You
guys have to do your job. And I guess
I'm going to have to contact somebody.
So, that's fair. I mean, cuz I know how
this stuff works. I mean, I I I
I just can't believe it. That's I mean,
we we understand that. I mean, if we
were in your position, I mean, we would
feel the same way. I just can't even
believe it. I mean, it's just I mean,
I'm shocked. I'm really shocked that
somebody would be blame saying that I
did this. I mean, we had a fight and so
I went and killed her. I mean, come on.
Well,
that's okay. All right. Well, thanks for
giving me the courtesy. I wish it Thanks
for your time. Yeah. Thank you. All
right, Stephanie. Take care. All
right.
Crazy. Thank you.
That is crazy.
I am.
This is absolutely crazy. I want to see
stuff.
This is insane. Okay,
give me one sec.
Okay, Stephanie, you know you have the
right to remain silent. Do you
understand? Yes. Anything you say may be
used against you in court. Do you
understand? Yes. You have the right to
the presence of an attorney before and
during any question. Do you understand?
Yes. If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be appointed for you free of
charge before any questioning if you
want. Do you understand? Yes. You want
to talk to us right now? No. Okay. All
right. Okay. This is crazy. This is abs
like I'm like in shock. I'm totally in
shock.